thebillioncoin.info 2016-12-03

# TBC | Privacy Policy

**Privacy policy**

'The Official Thebillioncoin.com Web Site' is committed to protecting the privacy of its visitors. The policy statement provides our visitors with an overview of the measures we have taken to show our commitment to this policy.

**Personal Information**

We collect the personal data that you volunteer on forms which you submit to us for on-line competitions and in emails that you send to us. In addition we automatically gather details of browser types and IP addresses of the users who visit our site. We do not release this information to any outside party, except in suspected fraud cases.

When fraudulent activity is suspected, we may release the users details to the party that the user has been trading with. This is done only if there is strong evidence that actual trade has happened.

**Opting Out**

Users who join the forum will automatically receive Newsletters. Should users later decide to opt-out from receiving this information please contact us and you will be removed from our database and no longer receive future communication.

**Correct/Update**

You may request that we amend any personal data that we are holding about you which is factually inaccurate. You can email us stating your wishes.

**Public Forums/Chat Room**

This web site has a message board and chat room available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas become public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Thebillioncoin.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

**Competitions**

Thebillioncoin.com may occasionally run competitions with other web sites and we will ask visitors for their contact information. Any information that you supply will be held in the strictest confidence and will only be used in conjunction with the competition. In order for visitors to take part in the competitions you must be a member of the Thebillioncoin Forum.

**Data retention policy**

Thebillioncoin.com user data is stored three months after deleting the user account. 

Messages and file attachments related to the trade are stored 90 days after closing the trade. 

**Contacting The Web Site**

If you have any questions about this Privacy statement, the practices, or your dealing with this web site, please contact us and your enquiry will be dealt with as soon as possible.

\----------- 

**Trading**

**Buying TBC**

When a user buying TBC with traditional electronic payment methods using the escrow service, the buyer is required to provide correct reference message when paying. Bitcoin sellers are not required to release TBC paid with an incorrect reference. This is to prevent fraud.

Buyer should be ready to prove his/her identity, when buying TBC online and the payment method is reversible.

**Accounts**

A user can only act on his own behalf. No Thebillioncoin.com account can be used to act as an intermediary or broker. A user can only use his own trading accounts to trade at Thebillioncoin.com. A user account must not contain misleading information about the user, including, but not limited to having non-personal phone number or faking the country of origin. A user is not allowed to share his or hers account access with any other person or entity without prior approval from thebillioncoin.com administrator. Sharing account access with any 3rd party might result your Thebillioncoin account(s) to be terminated.

**Communication**

Hate-speech and abusive language is strictly forbidden on Thebillioncoin.com. Any user account that engages in abusive language or hate-speech can be banned.
